05/10/2022 16:56 Privacy Policy - DYNSEO - brain training apps -memory games

https://www.dynseo.com/en/privacy-policy/ 1/3

Privacy Policy

Introduction

With the development of new tools of communication, it is important to payattention to private data protection. Which is why we are committed torespecting the privacy of the personal information we collect on our differentour brain training applications: COCO THINKS and COCO MOVES, COCO PENSE eCOCO SI MUOVE, Scarlett, Clint, Edith, Joe, Roberto, Sofia, Annelies, Carmen,Fernando, Zhiqu and Iqu, The Rolling Ball, Top Culture / Top Kids developed byDYNSEO.

Information Collection and Use

Personal information about an individual may include the following:

Last nameFirst nameEmailGender / SexAge / Date of birth

We may collect information through forms and thanks to the interactivityexisting between you and our website. We also use, as mentioned hereafter,cookies and/or surveys to collect information about you.

Forms and interactive features:

Your personal information is collected through the use of forms, such as:

aa

05/10/2022 16:56 Privacy Policy - DYNSEO - brain training apps -memory games

https://www.dynseo.com/en/privacy-policy/ 2/3

Registration to the website,Registration within the apps.

We use the collected information for the following purposes:

Contact informationPerformance statistics

The DYNSEO brand is a registered trademark.

The DYNSEO apps have processed by the CNIL, who conducted June 11, 2013under the number 1679021.

The websites www.dynseo.com et www.stimart.com are hosted by OVH, locatedat 2 rue Kellermann – 59100 Roubaix – France.

Right of objection and erasure

We are committed to providing you with a right of objection and erasureregarding your personal information.

The right to object is understood ad being the possibility offered to the Internetusers to refuse that their personal information be used for certain purposesmentioned at the time of collection.

The right to erasure is understood as being the possibility offered to Internetuser to ask that their personal information no longer appear, for example, in amailing list.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us by email at the following addresses:

by mail at this address: 6 rue du Docteur Finlay, 75015 Paris,by email at justine.sauquet@dynseo.com by phone at this number:+33966938422.

Website section: https://www.stimart.com/

Right of access

We grant you the right of access and rectification to your personal data, if youwish to consult, modify or even delete information.

The exercise of this right will be made by mail to the address:

by mail at this address: 6 rue du Docteur Finlay, 75015 Paris,

05/10/2022 16:56 Privacy Policy - DYNSEO - brain training apps -memory games

https://www.dynseo.com/en/privacy-policy/ 3/3

Rewards The coaches’ toolbox The Parents Academy

Ask for a quote Legal Notice Terms of Use

by email at: justine.sauquet@dynseo.com,Phone: +33666240826

Website section: https://www.stimart.com/

Security

Personal data that we collect, is stored in a secured environment. Peopleworking for us are required to respect the confidentiality of personal data. Toensure its security, we use the following measures:

SSL protocol (Secure Sockets Layer)Access management – Authorized personAccess management – person concernedComputer backupLog in/ Password

We are committed to maintaining a high level of confidentiality by incorporatingthe latest technological innovations to ensure confidentiality of your data.However, since no mechanism provides maximum security, some risk is alwayspresent when using the Internet to transmit personal information.

Legislation

We undertake to respect the legislative provisions set out in Law 78-17“INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, DATA FILES AND CIVIL LIBERTIES.”

All Internet user dispose of the right of objection (Article 38 of the above-mentioned law), the right of access (Article 39, 41 and 42 of the above-mentioned law) and of rectification (Article 40 of the above-mentioned law)regarding their personal data.
